ccjk.com 2019-06-22

# Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  
**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**What do we use your information for?**

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**  
By using our website, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on May 29, 2018.

**Accessing data with compliance to GDPR**  
With the new GDPR relevant privacy policies being followed at Mars translation, we are going to follow a protocol in accordance to which there will be complete privacy given to the clients at Mars translation. For the clientele, they will be able to access the data and change it at any point that they want. They will have the ability to download their data, edit their data, as well as modify their data to their likings.

**Changing the Data**  
To change the data, the user needs to Log In the three Mars profiles and click on the My Profile button on the drop-down menu on the top right. Once they are on the page they can press the download button on the bottom left to get their data. Likewise, if they wish to modify their data, They edit it on the My Profile page.

**GDPR Compliant Practice at CCJK**  
As of May 29, 2018, CCJK Pvt. Ltd are compliant with the updated General Data Protection regulation  
GDPR extend the rights of clients in regards to data privacy rights concerning all of its European clients, this gives our clients a better handle on the power to control their data.Companies that provide services, and process personal data of their European clients, must comply with all the set of GDPR regulations. There are specific and clear requirements that these companies must meet and basic rights that European individuals can exercise with these companies. More information about GDPR can be found in the official GDPR European Union’s website:  
For more information concerning the protocols of GDPR, Visit their website.  
At CCJK Translation, We have appointed a Data Protection Officer to manage and supervise the fulfillment of all GDPR requirements, and assist any inquiries from individuals. The DPO can be reached at info@ccjk.com  
Functions to support GDPR requirements:  
CCJK Translation is committed to assist all customers managing their archived data.  
You may also choose to permanently delete all your data.  
This Privacy Policy was updated on May 29, 2018

## Over 95% of our clients recommend  
our language services to others

Get Free Quote
